希望黎明能早點到來
Say the dawn is drawing near
告訴我：「太陽很快就會出現」
Tell me that the sun will soon appear
陽光閃耀，宛如黃金
Beam of light, or ray of gold
黃色布滿了每個角落
Yellow passing all around the world
兩眼開開的你不會懂
You don't know until you've seen it blind
少了希望還有什麼用
It won't show if all your faith has died
艷麗的太陽
Luz del sol (Light of Sun)
明亮的月亮
Destello de la Luna (Gleam of the Moon)
餘光已悄悄離去
Aftershine has come and gone
我們還以為，太陽仍在天上
Some of us still feel it's going on
離別會有誰不懂
Separate everybody knows
但兩眼闔上，誰看得出區別
But there's no difference if your eyes are closed
我們總是能找到出路
Somehow we all find our way around
突然我們就這樣迷路
Now and then we're nowhere to be found
艷麗的太陽
Luz del sol (Light of Sun)
明亮的月亮
Destello de la Luna (Gleam of the Moon)
艷麗的太陽
Luz del sol (Light of Sun)
明亮的月亮
Destello de la Luna (Gleam of the Moon)